(100) Total
(10) Game UI (not required to be fancy)
    (5) Visible game board with the specified squares in three layers.
    (5) Visible player tokens, player's deeds and chance/community cards and balance.

(15) Debug functionality - CHANGE IN THE SOURCE CODE IS NOT ACCEPTED. You need to provide a debug GUI with the following properties:
        (12) Enable players to start from given 
            (3) squares 
            (3) balance
            (3) deed cards with given amount of buildings
            (3) chance/community cards (only keepable ones) etc.
        (3) Enable us to determine next dice values.

(20) Roll dice and move to the next square
    (2) Move according to Mr.
 Monopoly
    (2) Move according to Bus
    (3) Pass train station 
    (2) Pass GO square 
    (2) Pass payday.
    (2) Land on Holland Tunnel.
    (2) Land on Jail.
    (3) Land on Cab Square.
    (2) Land on tax refund.
  
(5) Build a house/hotel/skyscraper
    - Check all deeds of the same color are bought before building a house.
    - Before building a new house all the other properties of the same color should have at least same number of houses with this one.
    - Check 4 houses are built on each property of the same color before building a hotel.
    - Check no building can be built on utilities etc.

(5) Get out of jail:
    - By a chance/community card.
    - By rolling a double.
    - By paying fee.50$
    - By staying there in 3 turns without rolling a double.

(7) Buy/sell/mortgage title deeds/buildings
    (2) Sell properties. Check that there are no buildings on the property before selling it (not necessary for mortgaging though)
    (3) Mortgage a property and leave the mortgage on a property by paying the mortgage amount.
    (2) Sell buildings (selling hotel replaces it with 4 houses, skyscraper with a hotel etc).

(8) Pay rent - according to the rules (in Ultimate Monopoly)
    (2) Pay rent if 2 of the same colors owned (majority ownership).
    (2) Pay rent if all of the same colors are owned (monopoly).
    (2) Pay rent if house/hotel/skyscraper is built.
    (2) Pay rent for utilities.

(30) Chance and community chest cards
    Chance Cards:
    (5) Hurricane makes landfall! Remove 1 house from each property in any player's one color group. Downgrade Skyscrapers to Hotels.
    (5) Property taxes! Pay $5 to the pool for each unmortgaged property you own. 
    (5) Mardi Gras! All players must move to Canal Street

    Community Cards:
    (5) Assessed for Street Repairs: $25 per cab-transit station, $40 per house $115 per hotel and $100 per skyscraper.
    (5) House condemned: Sell a house 1/2 price you paid for it. (Do nothing if you have no houses) 
    (5) Special Online Pricing: Next time you land on anyone else's railroad only pay 1/2 the rent.   
